gamesamba.com 2011-06-19

# Privacy - Game Samba

GameSamba Privacy Policy

Contents

This policy covers how GameSamba, Inc. ("GameSamba") treats personal information that GameSamba collects and receives through its website and communications, related to your use of GameSamba products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, including your name, address, age, email address, phone number, preferences and other related information that is not otherwise publicly available. 

Information Collection and Use

GameSamba collects personal information when you register with GameSamba, when you use GameSamba products or services, and when you visit GameSamba.com web pages or the pages of certain GameSamba partners. GameSamba may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, age range, zip code, etc. Once you register with GameSamba and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

GameSamba collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 

GameSamba automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, GameSamba cookie information, and the page you request. 

GameSamba uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

If you elect to use GameSamba's referral service for informing a friend about our site or particular features or content, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. GameSamba will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit GameSamba. GameSamba stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

When purchasing game items or subscriptions to our games, you will have the choice to pay by credit card, PayPal, mobile phone, bill to your home phone or ISP or any other e-commerce available today or in the future. We will collect the required information for each payment method, however, this information will be kept confidential. 

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy: 

GameSamba recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. The GameSamba Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. GameSamba does not target its activities or the GameSamba Site to children under 13. GameSamba does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

GameSamba does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

1.We provide the information to trusted partners who may assist us or work on behalf of or with GameSamba under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help GameSamba communicate with you about offers from GameSamba and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. You have the right to opt out of these communications upon notifying us via email at support@GameSamba.com

2\. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

3\. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of GameSamba's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

4\. We transfer information about you if GameSamba is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, GameSamba will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Passive Means to Collect Information

To permit your efficient use of our websites, products and services, GameSamba uses cookies (small files stored in your computer), which let us know how you accessed our web site(s) and let us know that you are a prior customer (so that you will not have to re-enter all of the information previously provided to us every time you access our sites). GameSamba (or third parties on our behalf) may also use web beacons, which are transparent images that have been placed on a web page or an e-mail message, and send a signal that allows us to determine when a page has been visited, or an e-mail opened. Web beacons do not contain or collect personal information. The information that we do collect is used to allow us to better understand our customers' usage patterns, and to help us determine how they accessed our website(s). This information, in turn, allows us to improve our products to better meet your needs, and to enhance our communications with you. 

Communications from GameSamba

For everyone 13 years of age and over, certain communications from GameSamba, such as service announcements, and administrative messages are considered part of GameSamba membership and you may not opt out of receiving them. In particular those who register with us for beta testing GameSamba games agree to receive communications regarding these games as a part of their beta membership. 

All other emails from GameSamba will include a URL or email address where you can unsubscribe from future mailings. All new users are opted in to receive information from GameSamba and other affiliated company. You can change your contact preferences, personal information or delete your GameSamba account by visiting your Account page. 

Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

GameSamba may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your GameSamba account, if we have collected it, or by placing a prominent notice on our site. If you do not agree with these updates to the policy, or are no longer in compliance with the requirements, you are obligated to terminate your GameSamba Account immediately and cancel any services for which you have signed up. Your continued use of the GameSamba Service following any revision to this policy constitutes your complete and irrevocable acceptance of any and all such changes. 

How to Contact Us

While we strive for error free performance, we cannot always catch an unintended privacy issue. As a result, we encourage your questions and comments about any privacy concerns. Please direct them to us by an email to support@gamesamba.com. 

Privacy Statement Last Updated: December 16, 2010
